gun.deals 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy | gun.deals

  * Apps 47, INC
  * P.O. Box 13,
  * Germantown, OH 45327-0013

Welcome to the website of , located at (hereinafter “Company, “We”, “Us”, “Our”.) We thank You (any visitor to Our web site and hereinafter "You" or "Your") for visiting Our site and considering Our products and services.

gun.deals is a site where users and visitors share the best gun related deals that they  
find across the web. gun.deals is not selling firearms, ammunition or accessories. We  
simply browse the web for the best deals available for purchase online or in retail  
stores. Click on the Visit Deal on the product page and it will take you to the seller's  
website where you can purchase that particular product.

The following policy explains how information about You is used and protected. As stated in Our Terms of Service, Our Privacy Policy forms part of Your legal agreement with Us. By using this website or by Your agreement with this policy that You clicked, signifies that You agree with all terms of this Policy.

We want to assure all of Our customers that whenever information is used, it is done  
with discretion. The safeguarding of customer information is an issue We take  
seriously at gun.deals. To affirm Our continuing commitment to the proper use of  
customer information, We have set forth the following Privacy Policy.

## INFORMATION COLLECTED

### Non-Personal Information

When You use Our web site, Our servers may automatically collect certain Non- Personal Information such as: Your IP address, Your operating system or Your browser.

### Our Use of Cookies

We may use Cookies to store or retrieve information. Cookies are a small piece of text stored on Your browser which may allow Us to identify You upon return to the web site or to remember specific information such as Your display options. Cookies are neither a virus nor spy-ware. You hereby authorize the use of cookies by Us.

### No Information Collected from Children

We do not intentionally collect Personal Information from children who are younger than the age of majority in Your jurisdiction.

### Personal Information Collected

The Personal Information We may collect and store is the information that You voluntarily disclose to Us, including but not limited to; any information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with, a particular individual, such as: (1) first and last name; (2) home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town; (3) email address; (4) telephone number; (5) a government issued identifier; (6) any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual; or (7) information concerning a user that the web site or online service collects online from the user and maintains in personally identifiable form in combination with an identifier described in this subdivision. Personal Information does not include publicly available information that is lawfully made available to the general public from federal, state, or local government records.

### Third Party Information

Our Web site may contain links or display advertising from third parties. Non-Personal and Personal Information You voluntarily provide to third parties through links on Our web site may be shared with Us by Our advertisers and other third parties. In addition, We may receive Personal Information from co-registration partners when You have voluntary agreed to allow a third party to share their data. We have no control over the privacy practices of these third parties. Please be sure to read and accept the Privacy Policy on any web site You visit.

## HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We may use Your Personal Information for any legal purpose in Our sole discretion, including but not limited to; membership, registration, log-in, or order fulfillment purposes. You hereby agree that We may also use Your Personal Information to contact You by phone, U.S. mail or email.

## DISSEMINATION OF INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION

You hereby agree that We may transfer Personal Information to third parties for order fulfillment, to respond to Legal Processes or governmental requests for information, or for any other legal purpose.

## STORAGE AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

### Information Storage

We store Your Personal Information on Our computers, and We believe We have reasonable security measures in place to protect Your Personal Information including encryption of any personally identifying information. However, We cannot guarantee that Our security measures will prevent Our computers from being accessed without authorization and Your Personal Information stored on them stolen, deleted or changed. We assume no responsibility for such unauthorized actions.

### Security Breach Notice

For any unencrypted data that We maintain that includes Personal Information, We will notify You of any unencrypted Personal Information that was, or is reasonably believed to have been, acquired by an unauthorized person. The type of information that triggers the notice requirement is an individual's name plus one or more of the following: Social Security number, driver's license or a government issued identifier, financial account numbers, medical information or health insurance information, as well as any complete login information.

## DO NOT TRACK REQUESTS

While Your browser may contain a “do not track” signal or other mechanism that provides You the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information or about Your Internet activities over time and across third- party sites or online services, Our systems are not set up to accommodate Your browser’s request.

## DISPOSAL OF CUSTOMER RECORDS

When the time comes to dispose of Customer Records; We will shred, erase or otherwise modify the personal information when disposing of Customer Records under Our control.

## PRIVACY POLICY REGULATIONS FOR RESIDENTS OF THE EUROPEAN UNION UNDER THE GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)

We are pleased to have customers who are residents of the European Union countries and Great Britain. If You are a resident of the European Union or Great Britain We have initiated the following rules just for You in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

It is Our intent to provide this information to You in a concise, transparent, intelligible and easily accessible form, using clear and plain language.

You understand and agree that You are still responsible to follow the Privacy Policy of Our site as stated above. However, if there is any conflict between Our Privacy Policy and the GDPR then the regulations shall apply, and You have the right to have Your requests under the processed without undue delay, and the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling.

Our company is a data controller. We have designated a Data Protection Officer for Us who has the duty to: Ensure by contract that third parties to whom the company transfers personal information will adequately protect the information and use it only for specified lawful purposes, protect Your personal data using appropriate security measures, notify authorities of personal data breaches, obtain appropriate consents for processing data, ensure proper response to Your GDPR requests, keep records detailing data processing, train privacy personnel and employees, and to audit and update Our Privacy Policies. If You have any questions about Your Privacy Rights under the GDPR and Our Privacy Policy please feel free to contact Our Data Protection Officer by email to [customerservice@gun.deals](mailto:customerservice@gun.deals).

Your Personal Data is being collected when required for the functionality of Our site; as well as for the purpose of fulfilling Your order and processing Your payment. Shipping and payment processing may be provided by a third party to whom We will provide Your data for this purpose.

Your data will be kept in Our files for approximately two years from the time You last logged into Our site.

You have the right to request access to Your data stored by Us and to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement. taking into account the purposes of the processing. Should you elect to exercise this right we will update your changes with any third parties to whom we have shared your data.

You have the right to the rectification or erasure of Your personal data stored by Us or the restriction of processing concerning Your data. Should you elect to exercise this right we will update your changes with any third parties to whom we have shared your data.

You have a right to data portability and to have the personal data which You have provided to Us forwarded directly to another controller where technically feasible.

You may also lodge a complaint with Your country’s supervisory authority if You believe Your rights are not being properly handled under the DGPR. You also have the right to know from which source the personal data originated, and if applicable, whether it came from publicly accessible sources.

## PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES FOR OUR COMPANY

This Privacy Policy is effective as of September 17, 2018. We reserve the right to revise this policy from time to time without prior notice. You will be notified of any material changes in Our Privacy Policy either by email or by a conspicuous posting on Our Web site.
